<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on E-nzym3 Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on E-nzym3 Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:33:52 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GOAD - Game of Active Directory - Walkthrough</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/goad_walkthrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:33:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/goad_walkthrough/</guid>
      
      <description>Using Ludus and GOAD To Create Active Directory Firing Range As a penetration tester, it is crucial to have a stable, easily deployable, and accessible lab in which you can test various attack methods, exploits, and more. I have, in the past, built home labs from scratch using VMWare and a bunch of VMs running simultaneously on an old laptop. While that works pretty well when you are starting out, it can quickly get convoluted and annoying to manage.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing: Mitty</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mitty_intro-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:05:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mitty_intro-2024/</guid>
      
      <description>A Github Commit Bruteforce Tool used to find deleted or dereferenced commits! --&gt; Get Mitty Here &lt;-- The recent Defcon 2024 conference in Las Vegas hosted a Cloud Capture-The-Flag (CTF) event in which I participated with several of my work colleagues. I took on a couple of Git-related challenges as I never really interacted with Git from a CTF perspective but figured this would be a great way to learn more about Git and Github.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WarDriver Pi - Build Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/wardriver-pi_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:08:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/wardriver-pi_2024/</guid>
      
      <description>A Guide To Building Your Own WarDriving/WiFi Assessment Raspberry Pi As penetration testers, we often have to travel onsite to perform various engagements. I recently was tasked with performing a wireless assessment for a client, but realized I did not want to walk around the client’s site with a laptop in hand, as that is just plain cumbersome. As such, I decided to put on my thinking hat, dust off some of the Raspberry Pi 3’s that I had laying around , and turn them into something useful that may just solve my immediate issue.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s This All About?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:08:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/intro/</guid>
      
      <description>Intro I have always been interested in things… many things. My mind is a constant torrent of ideas, questions, “hmm” thoughts. These often lead me on multi-hour research journeys. While learning many things can often seem like a good thing, it only is if you remember what you learned 2 or 3 days later.
Due to this, note taking has become a big part of my life, at least for the things I’m planning to remember days, months, or years later.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
